const questions = [
{
"question" : "Anthony Reid set the fastest time at the Goodwood Festival of Speed’s hill climb event this year, but what was he driving?",
"option_A" : "Lexus",
"option_B" : "Porsche",
"option_C" : "Noble",
"option_D" : "Aston Martin",
"answer"  : 3
},

{
"question" : "The Porsche 911 GT3 Cup uses a 3.8-litre boxer engine to compete in the worldwide Carrera Cups. How much power does the 991-generation racecar produce?",
"option_A" : "160 HP",
"option_B" : "260 HP",
"option_C" : "360 HP",
"option_D" : "460 HP",
"answer"  : 4
},

{
"question" : "Who built the electric motors used by the grid for the first season of Formula E?",
"option_A" : "Tesla",
"option_B" : "Nissan",
"option_C" : "McLaren",
"option_D" : "Mercedes Benz",
"answer"  : 3
},

{
"question" : "Sebastien Loeb has consecutively won the most WRC drivers’ championships, but who’s the second consecutive winner?",
"option_A" : "Sebastien Ogier",
"option_B" : "Tommi Makinen",
"option_C" : "Miki Baision",
"option_D" : "Walter Rohrl",
"answer"  : 2
},

{
"question" : "As Porsche raced to a 17th Le Mans victory last month, it helped Michelin secure its 24th win, but what year was Michelin’s first?",
"option_A" : "1923",
"option_B" : "1933",
"option_C" : "1943",
"option_D" : "1953",
"answer"  : 1
},

{
"question" : "In which year were the chicanes introduced along the Mulsanne straight at Le Mans to slow the cars down?",
"option_A" : "1970",
"option_B" : "1980",
"option_C" : "1990",
"option_D" : "2000",
"answer"  : 3
},

{
"question" : "Just one city will host two Formula E races in the 2015-2016 season: which is it?",
"option_A" : "Moscow",
"option_B" : "Berlin",
"option_C" : "London",
"option_D" : "Beunos Aires",
"answer"  : 3
},

{
"question" : "Which constructor holds the most wins in the WRC?",
"option_A" : "Lancia",
"option_B" : "Mitsubishi",
"option_C" : "Peugeot",
"option_D" : "Citreon",
"answer"  : 4
},

{
"question" : "Mazda is the only Japanese manufacturer to have ever won at Le Mans. Which year was it?",
"option_A" : "1971",
"option_B" : "1981",
"option_C" : "1991",
"option_D" : "2001",
"answer"  : 3
},

{
"question" : "Who won the 2003 Porsche Carrera Cup Great Britain?",
"option_A" : "Barry Horne",
"option_B" : "Richard Westbrook",
"option_C" : "Jason Templeman",
"option_D" : "Jonathan Cocker",
"answer"  : 1
},

]